{"questionList":[{"question":"What is the function of home button?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":" The home button to make you see the home screen as it is displayed."},{"key":2,"answer":"The home button is making you see the home screen as it is displayed."},{"key":3,"answer":" The home button makes you see the home screen as it is displayed."},{"key":4,"answer":" The home button make you see the home screen as it is displayed."}],"correct":3},{"question":"What is the function of touch screen?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"The function of a touch screen is to displayingall applications buttons."},{"key":2,"answer":"The function of a touch screen is for displayingall applications buttons."},{"key":3,"answer":"The function of a touch screen is for display all applications buttons."},{"key":4,"answer":"The function of a touch screen is for displays all applications buttons."}],"correct":2},{"question":"What is the function of volume button?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"Volume button has a function to increase and decrease the volume."},{"key":2,"answer":" Volume button has a function to increasing and decrease the volume."},{"key":3,"answer":"Volume button has a function for increase and decrease the volume."},{"key":4,"answer":"Volume button has a function is increase and decrease the volume."}],"correct":1},{"question":"What is the function of front camera?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":" The front camera to help you to focus on the picture that you want to capture."},{"key":2,"answer":" The front camera helping you to focus on the picture that you want to capture."},{"key":3,"answer":"The front camera help you to focus on the picture that you want to capture."},{"key":4,"answer":" The front camera helps you to focus on the picture that you want to capture."}],"correct":4},{"question":" What is the function of sleep\/wake button?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"This button has a function to save the energy of the phone battery."},{"key":2,"answer":"This button has a function for save the energy of the phone battery."},{"key":3,"answer":"This button has a function saves the energy of the phone battery."},{"key":4,"answer":"This button has a function to saving the energy of the phone battery."}],"correct":1},{"question":"What is the function of status bar?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"The function of the status bar is for indicate a specific information about the phone, for example signal strength or wi-fi connection."},{"key":2,"answer":" The function of the status bar is for indicating a specific information about the phone, for example signal strength or wi-fi connection."},{"key":3,"answer":" The function of the status bar is to indicating a specific information about the phone, for example signal strength or wi-fi connection."},{"key":4,"answer":"The function of the status bar is for indicates a specific information about the phone, for example signal strength or wi-fi connection."}],"correct":2},{"question":"What is the function of SIM card tray?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"This tray has a function for puts your SIM card."},{"key":2,"answer":"This tray has a function for put your SIM card."},{"key":3,"answer":"This tray has a function for putting your SIM card."},{"key":4,"answer":" This tray has a function to putting your SIM card."}],"correct":3},{"question":"What is the function of dock connector?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"The dock connector connects the battery charger to the phone."},{"key":2,"answer":"The dock connector connecting the battery charger to the phone."},{"key":3,"answer":"The dock connector connect the battery charger to the phone."},{"key":4,"answer":"The dock connector to connect the battery charger to the phone."}],"correct":1},{"question":"What is the function of speaker?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":" The speaker to enable you to hear the voice of your caller or the music that you play."},{"key":2,"answer":"The speaker enabling you to hear the voice of your caller or the music that you play."},{"key":3,"answer":"The speaker enable you to hear the voice of your caller or the music that you play."},{"key":4,"answer":" The speaker enables you to hear the voice of your caller or the music that you play."}],"correct":3},{"question":"What is the function of camera lens?","answerList":[{"key":1,"answer":"The camera lens helps you to focus on the picture that you want to capture."},{"key":2,"answer":"The camera lens helping you to focus on the picture that you want to capture."},{"key":3,"answer":"The camera lens help you to focus on the picture that you want to capture."},{"key":4,"answer":"The camera lens to help you to focus on the picture that you want to capture."}],"correct":1}]}